So, here's the one
that's water cooled.
OK, don't blink.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's the speed
of sound in glass,
which is, I think, about three
times faster than the speed
of sound in air.
So you can't see it.
But there is some great
high-speed video--
maybe some of you have
seen that online--
of Prince Rupert
drops exploding.
And actually up in
the Edgerton Center
they have a camera
that can catch that,
and they've got some
really cool video.
I'm going to leave this.
This is a very
cool fragment that
shows the fracture, the
failure pattern, which
is really interesting.
It fails from the
center of the drop
radially out at an
angle that looks
to be about a 45-degree angle.
You can probably explain that.
That will be on
the quiz tomorrow.
[LAUGHTER]
45 degree [INAUDIBLE]?
Was there a question?
I'm going to do one more
just in case anybody blinked,
and then I'm going
to be on my way.